# **YURIY KOSHYK**

### PRODUCT DESIGNER

With 4+ years of experience I bring together design finesse and technical prowess to craft impactful digital experiences focusing on business and user needs. Out of work I enjoy movies, books, play basketball and do street photography.

**PORTFOLIO** 

@YURIYKOSH

Βē

+420 776 182 501

@YURIYKOSH



@YURIY-KOSHYK

## **WORK HISTORY**

YURIY.KOSHYK@GMAIL.COM

#### PRODUCT DESIGNER

KOSH | Mar 2020 - current

- Delivered 15+ projects, focusing on UX/UI design to drive business growth and user satisfaction:
- · Led full design research cycles, including user research, prototyping, and usability testing;
- · Translated business requirements and market insights into innovative design solutions;
- · Created high-performance digital products aligned with business metrics;
- · Monitored KPIs to optimise designs based on user feedback and data-driven insights.

#### **HEAD OF SYSTEMS & IT**

DF Druckluft-Fachhandel GmbH | Aug 2023 - Jul 2024

- $\cdot\,$  Leading the tech side of a multimillion e-commerce company;
- · Increased company revenue by 10% with optimization of UX and system processes;
- · Effectively managed internal cross-functional team + 4 external partners;
- · Implemented the Agile methodology in the majority of the departments;
- · Successfully completed the company migration to Atlas Copco Group.

#### **UX/UI DESIGNER & FRONTEND DEVELOPER**

Heimdal Data ApS | Dec 2022 - Jul 2023

- · Adhered to design standards and collaborate with stakeholders;
- · Developed user-friendly interfaces with a focus on user experience;
- $\cdot\,$  Wrote clean and scalable code that increase website performance;
- · Conduct user research and gather requirements for the design process;
- $\cdot\,$  Brought creative design trends and new technologies to the company's projects.

## PROJECT EXPERIENCE

**EVENTPOS** [Figma, Adobe Creative Suite]

Role: Product Designer

Mobile payment solution specifically designed for events.

**DF DRUCKLUFT-FACHHANDEL** [Agile, Azure, PowerBI, HTML, SASS, JS, SQL, Figma, Adobe CS]

Role: Head of Systems & IT

E-commerce for complete compressed air solutions (a part of Atlas Copco Group).

#### **SKILLS**

**UX/UI** Design

**UX Research** 

User Interview

Usability Testing & A/B Testing

Wireframing & Prototyping

Design Systems - 0 to 1

Management

HTML5 / CSS3 / SASS

JavaScript / React / Next.js

Adobe Creative Suite

Figma, Blender, ProtoPie, Hotjar

**Google Analytics** 

#### **SOFT SKILLS**

Attention to details

Self & team management

Communication Skills

Problem-solving

Creativity

English, German, Ukrainian, Russian

#### **EDUCATION**

PR)(TR

UX Design Medium

Projector Institute



Frontend Developer



Media Communications Diploma

Humber College



Foundation in Computing Bournemouth University International College